[{"id":0,"title":"pudding","description":"how to pudding","questions":[{"question":"taste","rightAnswer":"chocolate","wrongAnswer1":"strawberry","wrongAnswer2":"vanilla","wrongAnswer3":"jizz"},{"question":"where","rightAnswer":"home ","wrongAnswer1":"in ma belly","wrongAnswer2":"restaurant","wrongAnswer3":"up yours"}],"avgScore":1.03,"amountPlayed":30},{"id":1,"title":"offline","description":"smlfdkj","questions":[{"question":"oijf√¢oij","rightAnswer":"poij","wrongAnswer1":"poij","wrongAnswer2":"oij","wrongAnswer3":"poij"},{"question":"iugh","rightAnswer":"oug","wrongAnswer1":"ougy","wrongAnswer2":"ogy","wrongAnswer3":"ougy"}],"avgScore":0.83,"amountPlayed":6},{"id":2,"title":"oiug","description":"ouig","questions":[{"question":"lgyu","rightAnswer":"yug","wrongAnswer1":"oyg","wrongAnswer2":"oug","wrongAnswer3":"ougy"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":1},{"id":3,"title":"boiubzad","description":"liugbuyv","questions":[{"question":"livyg","rightAnswer":"luyvf","wrongAnswer1":"lufv","wrongAnswer2":"luyfv","wrongAnswer3":"luy"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":1},{"id":4,"title":"xc vbn,","description":"ijhbn","questions":[{"question":"lo","rightAnswer":"iujhn,","wrongAnswer1":"kiu","wrongAnswer2":"kloiuj","wrongAnswer3":"hjkoi"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":5,"title":"luyg","description":"luy","questions":[{"question":"uylg","rightAnswer":"luyg","wrongAnswer1":"olugy","wrongAnswer2":"luyg","wrongAnswer3":"uyg"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":1},{"id":6,"title":"asdf","description":"animal","questions":[{"question":"beep beep imma","rightAnswer":"sheep","wrongAnswer1":"human","wrongAnswer2":"cow","wrongAnswer3":"dogo"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":7,"title":"asdf","description":"animal","questions":[{"question":"beep beep imma","rightAnswer":"sheep","wrongAnswer1":"human","wrongAnswer2":"cow","wrongAnswer3":"dogo"}],"avgScore":1,"amountPlayed":1},{"id":8,"title":"asdf","description":"animal","questions":[{"question":"beep beep imma","rightAnswer":"sheep","wrongAnswer1":"human","wrongAnswer2":"cow","wrongAnswer3":"dogo"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":9,"title":"asdf","description":"animal","questions":[{"question":"beep beep imma","rightAnswer":"sheep","wrongAnswer1":"human","wrongAnswer2":"cow","wrongAnswer3":"dogo"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0},{"id":10,"title":"mljnhgv","description":"kgu","questions":[{"question":"yfogl","rightAnswer":"hjgoig","wrongAnswer1":"iyrd","wrongAnswer2":"ljhf","wrongAnswer3":"fhkv"}],"avgScore":0,"amountPlayed":0}]